<file>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Why should an early embryonic cell or a cell closely related to such an embryonic cell display markers that would provoke the immune system to attack</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The common perception seems to be that men pay no attention to their clothes; they might as well dress in the dark as they just throw on a pair of pants and a shirt!! Nothing could be more incorrect. Men take as much trouble over their clothes as women</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>They can push species to the brink of extinction, or throw a spanner into the complex web of life in an ecosystem. And according to some scientists, MMEs are on the rise and likely to become more common because of climate change</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>In addition to lithic analysis, the field prehistorian utilizes a wide range of techniques derived from multiple fields. The work of the archaeologist in determining the paleocontext and relative sequence of the layers is supplemented by the efforts of the geologic specialist in identifying layers of rock over geologic time, of the paleontological specialist in identifying bones and animals, of the palynologist in discovering and identifying plant species</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The acting, story, atmosphere and actions scenes are all amazing. If you haven't seen this movie see it right now! I went into this not expecting to much but I came out blown away, I cant imagine any movie being much better</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Derived from buckwheat, 2-HOBA stands out because of the way it seems to work—by influencing immune cells</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Kendall let the dress do all the talking because she kept her accessories simple. She wore green drop earrings that have a slight art-deco feel and paired it with a subtle silver ring</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>These cells can live a long time and can respond quickly following a second exposure to the same infections</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>On April 12, 1776, the revolutionary convention of North Carolina specifically authorized its delegates in the Congress to vote for independence</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The violence is extreme, especially when you consider Batman is essentially a children's comic. The movie revels in sadism and extreme violence</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The mid-15th-century invention of modern printing, employing movable type, revolutionized communication and facilitated ever wider dissemination of information, helping end the Middle Ages and ushering in the Scientific Revolution</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>After fittings at Chanel, showrooms including Film Fashion and Alta Moda, and with stylist Rachel Zoe, Kim was equipped to win the best dressed gold</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Another important agent is the B-cell, which produces antibodies that lock on to sites on the surface of bacteria or viruses and immobilise them until macrophages consume them</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Over the past few years, computers have become incredibly good at recognizing faces</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The art direction extends to a few Batman gadgets and some lo-fi emo make up on the Joker. No effort whatsoever was made to show Gotham as anything other than a generic American city</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>The bacteria carried a modified DNA repair protein that caused any mutations to glow yellow</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Valentino’s anorak is decorated with elaborate detailing, Kenzo’s comes in candy colours. Z Zegna’s sailing gear is as yellow as the sun and Hermes’ duffle coat is as sleek as they come. Practical and pretty: what a winning mix.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Our immune defences consist of a range of cells and proteins that detect invading micro-organisms and attack them. The first line of defence, however, consists of simple physical barriers like skin, which blocks invaders from entering your body</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>The oldest stone tools were excavated from the site of Lomekwi 3 in West Turkana, northwestern Kenya, and date to 3.3 million years old</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The way it is animated, the soundtrack, the characters, the story, the thrill and the suspense. All in one action-packed anime. One of the best so far</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Beginning in the 8th century BCE, the "Axial Age" saw the development of a set of transformative philosophical and religious ideas, mostly independently, in many different places</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>And a handy bag isn’t the only thing you can get your hands on. If a backpack doesn’t quite suit your style you can also pick up a purse (£68), baseball cap (£37) or even a pair of trainers (£191) all made out of used cement sacks</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The scientists involved stress that their work is only now beginning and warn that it will still take several years’ research</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>In these cities, a new era was born: the Renaissance. The Renaissance was a time of great intellectual and economic change, but it was not a complete “rebirth”: It had its roots in the world of the Middle Ages</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>After watching the whole first season, I am extremely disappointed</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>From the 3rd century CE, the Gupta dynasty oversaw the period referred to as ancient India's Golden Age</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>A fashion staple that has been around for decades and will no doubt remain for many, many more, everyone needs a pair of jeans that make them look and feel like a million dollars</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>It is one of the most important developments in the battle against cancer this century</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>After the fall of Rome, no single state or government united the people who lived on the European continent. Instead, the Catholic Church became the most powerful institution of the medieval period</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>There is so much that is wonderful about this drama. Excellent writing and acting. The locations and sets are uniquely fabulous. It doesn't feel like a British TV drama, more like an American road movie. Great pacing. A wonderful mix of humour, darkness and pathos. Truly fantastic</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Ancient history is the aggregate of past events from the beginning of recorded human history and extending as far as the Early Middle Ages or the Post-classical Era. The span of recorded history is roughly 5,000 years, beginning with Sumerian Cuneiform script, the oldest discovered form of coherent writing from the protoliterate period around the 30th century BC</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Comfortable, versatile and effortlessly stylish, a pair of white sneakers can be worn with everything from a simple jeans and T-shirt combo to smart tailoring, so don’t be too quick to ditch your go-to trainers. </body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Recently, however, researchers, including Hayday, have found an unexpected ally in their battle against autoimmune disease: cancer. It is an unexpected link, but a promising one</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>The phrase “Middle Ages” tells us more about the Renaissance that followed it than it does about the era itself. Starting around the 14th century, European thinkers, writers and artists began to look back and celebrate the art and culture of ancient Greece and Rome</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>The kids are okay. They've managed to portray the losers and the relationship between them decently enough- considering the running time. Again: more time is needed for better development. Much of what actually happened between the kids and It has been cut, but again - running time</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>They lasted from the early 2nd millennium to the 1st century BC</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>If it moves, shimmers or glitters while you walk, then wear it. From Saint Laurent’s cloud of a dress covered in white ostrich feathers and soft-shouldered coats shot through with sequins and floral embroidery at Dries van Noten and Rochas</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>However, on occasions they go too far. Instead of killing off invading organisms, our immune systems turn on our own tissue and attack it. Conditions such as type 1 diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, and lupus are all triggered in this way, very often with deeply unpleasant consequences.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>During the course of the night, the major and his men destroyed 12 enemy tanks, pushing back attack after attack from their sand dune with limited means of retaliation</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>"Stranger Things" blended the best parts of some of the great 80's sci-fi films from "E.T." to "Poltergeist" to "The Goonies" to my all time favorite, "Close Encounters of the Third Kind." It was simply brilliant, and brings you back to a time when you were still able to feel a sense of wonder</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fasion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>WHEN I FIRST saw a silk Maria Cornejo dress at the designer’s downtown New York City store in 2004, I didn’t even begin to get it</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>It was also the first time that mannish styles became fashionable. There was a trend for women wearing tuxedos and tailored suits. Coco Chanel borrowed hers from her boyfriend along with fisherman’s sweaters and tweeds</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>This complex, however, homes in on DNA landing pads that have specific molecular features. The enzyme in the standard CRISPR toolkit, called spCas9 for its natural source, the bacterium Streptococcus pyogenes, can only land on genome segments that have at one end a specific three-base trio: N, where N is any of DNA's four bases, followed by two guanines</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Those were, in our opinion, the greatest roulette wins in history. As you can see, anyone can win at roulette – from people who wager their life savings, to successful billionaires. Keep in mind that none of them used a particular strategy (except for Joseph, who was exploiting a biased wheel), they were just plain lucky</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>IT is a literal disaster and a slap in the face to anyone who actually read and cherishes the book. There are NO character backstories, nor character development at all</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fasion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Dress for Success: How Clothes Influence Our Performance?</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>And now that the motion picture was emerging, the new trends could reach more people faster than ever before. Hollywood was bursting into the popular consciousness with an explosion of film palaces going up across the world, and massive stars coming into their own</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>But researchers are divided over whether to test the more powerful immune-suppressing drugs that patients take for illnesses such as psoriasis, Crohn disease, and rheumatoid arthritis. Schiffrin argues that these drugs are too risky to use in hypertension, which people can live with for decades. We don't want to produce fatal symptoms in a patient … because we were playing around with their immune system</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Charles Wells was a small time crook and an overall shady person who enjoyed gambling. One night in 1891, he went to the world-famous Monte Carlo Casino Resort and started playing roulette. He had the winning streak of a lifetime – sources claim that he won 23 out of 30 consecutive spins</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>More of the same at the last film(s) but a lot more silly, more bad acting, more bad dialogue, more of a stupid story, more tongue in cheek humour, more ridiculous cameo appearances, more more more of exactly the same to the point that it's getting a bit dull for me</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fasion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Janique Dresses offers you an outstanding, stylish appearance with a collections that are ready to go for any special occasion</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>The 1920s was when “the modern woman’s wardrobe began,” Nothdruft says. Out went the tight corsets and bustles of the Edwardian era, as did the long, hugely impractical dresses, elaborate hair styles and hats of that time, and in came the shorter, drop-waisted dresses and easy-to-manage bobbed hairstyles</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>They infused immune-suppressing regulatory T cells into hypertensive mice and reported that the cells reined in blood pressure and reduced the amount of blood vessel damage the animals suffered. The data, at least in animal models, are compelling that the immune system is involved in hypertension</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The match was particularly memorable for Dennis Bergkamp's performance; he rolled back the years to set up the first three of Arsenal's seven goals</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Wow, what a terrible movie. This is the first movie I have ever went to that I seriously considered walking out of</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Rotten Tomatoes staff presents 200 essential movies to watch now, whether you're a film buff or just starting your journey into cinema! We culled choices across genres, film movements, and centuries, mixed with staff favorites to shake things up. Best of all, every movie on the list is Certified Fresh</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Prior to this, the T-shirt was, by and large, an undergarment meant to be worn beneath one’s ‘proper’ clothes, and was seldom regarded as an article in its own right. “It’s just a white T-shirt, but it already has that kind of disruptive potential,”</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>More than 1 billion people worldwide have high blood pressure, which promotes heart attacks, strokes, kidney damage, dementia, and other ailments. Current drugs include diuretics that reduce the amount of water in the body and ß blockers that decrease how much blood the heart pumps. Yet about 15% to 20% of patients don't improve</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Beginning in late 1941, the Germans began mass transports from the ghettoes in Poland to the concentration camps, starting with those people viewed as the least useful: the sick, old and weak and the very young</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>There are wacky characters and absurd plots to be sure, but all of that eventually takes a backseat to the fact that Bojack Horseman is, at heart, a nuanced and overtly depressing show about pain and self-loathing.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The films listed below have been cited by a variety of notable critics in varying media sources as being among the worst films ever made</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Effective at keeping one toasty in colder temperatures, it wasn’t exactly suited towards heat or warm weather. Frustrated with its design, workers cut them in half, tucking the top bit into the bottom.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Big females produce more eggs than little females, so for some species, such as clownfish, it's best to be a male early in life when more runty and then switch to a female later on</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Like the network of concentration camps that followed, becoming the killinggrounds of the Holocaust, Dachau was under the control of Heinrich Himmler, head of the elite Nazi guard, the Schutzstaffel (SS), and later chief of the German police</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The opening of the show is a succinct depiction of the general feeling expressed in every episode. I have frankly been tiring of the increasing" anti hero" complex penetrating the mainstream surface</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>In 2017, lousy movies proliferated like loopy Trump tweets. No week went by without a movie or three to leave us wondering when, exactly, Hollywood lost the ability to distinguish good from godawful</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Although T-shirt-like garments, such as the tunic, date back to ancient times, it was only recently (relatively speaking) that the T-shirt as it is now known first appeared. Its origins lie in the ‘union suit’, a sort of button-down onesie worn by both men and women (but particularly male workers) towards the end of the 19th Century in the US. </body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Fish are masters of reproductive resilience. About 450 species switch sexes over their lifetimes to maximize their number of offspring. The fish do so by undergoing hormonal changes that transform their organs from those of one sex to the other. Patterns of sex switching vary by species</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The word “Holocaust,” from the Greek words “holos” (whole) and “kaustos” (burned), was historically used to describe a sacrificial offering burned on an altar</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>After watching the second episode, I was left in shock about the jarring contrast from the first episode</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Automated image processing let them count the number of mutations and assess how well the cells were doing</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The style was also the perfect way for the rising bourgeoisie to show off their wealth. Men’s attire was relatively subdued at the time but if a man could afford to dress his wife in a crinoline, which required vast amounts of fabric and the help of a servant to put on, it would indicate access to a substantial income.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>So once a squirrel is nice and tubby, it enters hibernation, slashing its energy expenditure by 90%. Its body temperature drops to just above freezing and its heart rate falls to as low as 5 beats per minute, down from the usual 350 to 400.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>The following month, amid a wave of violence in which Parisian insurrectionists massacred hundreds of accused counterrevolutionaries, the Legislative Assembly was replaced by the National Convention, which proclaimed the abolition of the monarchy and the establishment of the French republic</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Beyond these philosophical aspects, the program is incredibly well produced and executed in my opinion. The characters and sets create convincing realities and I was never once drawn out of the story due to poor acting, scripting or characterizations.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Dead cells signaled a deadly mutation; slower growing cells signaled a detrimental change</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>In Western culture the lower parts of the body are not considered worthy, which is why women’s legs have been hidden for centuries under skirts and petticoats.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>As with many resilience strategies in nature, stealing genes has its costs. Sometimes microbes incorporate harmful genes instead of helpful ones. And much like a new player on a basketball team, the protein produced from an acquired gene may not mesh with the cell's other proteins. But unfortunately for patients, K. pneumoniae's strategy works all too well</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>As the 18th century drew to a close, France’s costly involvement in the American Revolution and extravagant spending by King Louis XVI (1754-1793) and his predecessor had left the country on the brink of bankruptcy</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>I have only seen the first two installments of this series and but was impressed enough to leave a review. Charlie Brooker has popped out of the internet at times when I least expect it revealing the more unsettling aspects of our culture through his program Screenwipe and others</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>So chic, studied and murky it resembles a cross between a Nike commercial and a bad Polish art film</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The return to a nipped-in waist, shown to its best advantage by the voluminous crinoline, in vogue from 1845 to 1870, drew attention to the upper body, which was considered “the most precious,” according to Denis Bruna, curator of the fashion department of the Musée des Arts Décoratifs in Paris.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>One small fragment of those 2-centimeter-long aquatic worms can rejuvenate the brain, skin, gut, and all the other functional organs. Again, stem cells are key, and a special set of genes active in muscles tells those stem cells what to do, activating growth and specialization genes in the right cells at the right time.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>A watershed event in modern European history, the French Revolution began in 1789 and ended in the late 1790s with the ascent of Napoleon Bonaparte</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>the wooden acting, the cruddy screenplay, the corny dialogue, the ridiculous script, the highly improbable storyline, were all just TOO much for us</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Mothers from middle class families are the perfect audience for this film</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>Ethnic Indian men's clothes have a huge global market. With the vast NRI community overseas the frequency of culture based social events has multiplied. </body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>About 30 research teams are probing how these salamanders do it. In the axolotl, they've found, various tissues work together to detect limb loss and coordinate regrowth. In the process, the animals reactivate the same genetic circuits that guided the formation of those structures during embryonic development, causing generalist stem cells to specialize</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>By 1948, the percentage of women in the U.S. workforce dipped to 32.7 percent, according to the U.S. Department of Labor, this despite a poll taken in the last few years of the war that suggested between 61 to 85 percent of women wanted to remain in their jobs when the war was over.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>As it turns out I was wrong, Black Panther was extremely average, I have no idea what these critics/review bots are talking about when they say that it is the best Marvel movie and worthy of "critical" praise as not just a super hero movie but as a movie in general</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Even a single cell lodged in a mouse’s lung produced a detectable glow, the researchers report today in Science. The team also inserted the enzyme’s genes directly into neurons of a marmoset monkey</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The best way to combine a fusion outfit is to mix and match various clothing options. One of the most sought after trends this season is the dhoti look.</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>negative</tone>
		<body>Our powers of regeneration are limited: Broken bones knit, wounds heal, and large parts of the liver can regenerate, but that's about it</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>Women may have saved the day during WWII, but when the war ended, things quickly changed. Soldiers were returning home and they needed jobs to help them get back on their feet and reacclimatize to civilian life</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>First of all, it is very clear that the production mindset behind Westworld is far from creating a cheap product with generic high bursts of tension/love/horror/excitement. It is full of deep human conflicts, that is if you are open to watch it with a clear mind</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>In the future, this kind of imaging technology could allow doctors to track transplanted cells or monitor the growth of tumors—all without the need for invasive surgery</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>fashion</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>The year 2016 experienced the worst sales growth rate of 2-3 per cent with stagnating profit margins. This is in stark contrast to the fashion industry's performance in the previous decade of 2005-2015, which saw the industry grow at a 5.5 per cent annual rate, according to the McKinsey Global Fashion Index</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>biology</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>He has two 15cm electrodes that run deep into his brain and create two bumps on his head which he affectionately refers to as "baby giraffe horns".</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>history</subject>
		<tone>neutral</tone>
		<body>America’s entry into World War II helped turn the tide for the Allies, but the quick mobilization also created a vacuum on the home front. At the same time that the country needed to ramp up industrial production to supply the American military machine, it was also sending hundreds of thousands of men who had previously filled this labor force overseas to fight</body>
	</reuters>
	<reuters>
		<subject>film</subject>
		<tone>positive</tone>
		<body>That is how I approached it, and my expectations were taken to another level. Westworld is, put simply, a contemporary screenplay masterpiece</body>
	</reuters>
</file>